{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Little Women","incorrectAnswers":["Buddenbrooks","David Copperfield","Jane Eyre"],"question":"In which book does 'Jo March' appear?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Walk This Way","incorrectAnswers":["Red Red Wine","A Case of U","Over the Rainbow"],"question":"Which song, originally recorded by Aerosmith, was later covered by Run-DMC?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Fauvist","incorrectAnswers":["Impressionist","Cubist","Surrealist"],"question":"What art movement was Maurice de Vlaminck part of, known for its bold use of color?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Bob Dylan","incorrectAnswers":["Bruce Springsteen","David Bowie","Neil Young"],"question":"Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Blood on the Tracks?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Wellington, New Zealand ","incorrectAnswers":["Canberra, Australia","Cape Town, South Africa","Santiago, Chile"],"question":"What is the world's most southerly capital?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Experience","incorrectAnswers":["Expertise","Extra Power","Express"],"question":"What Does The XP In The Operating System 'Windows XP' Actually Stand For?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"New South Wales","incorrectAnswers":["Northern Territories","Western Australia","Tasmania"],"question":"Which is the most populated state/territory in Australia?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Scandinavia","incorrectAnswers":["Britain","China","The Maghreb"],"question":"Where did the Vikings originate from?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Alaska","incorrectAnswers":["Hawaii","Puerto Rico","New Mexico"],"question":"In America, what became the 49th state to enter the union in 1959?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Rabat","incorrectAnswers":["Lagos","Kinshasa","Douala"],"question":"Which of these cities is in Morocco?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"\"Werewolves of London\" by Warren Zevon","incorrectAnswers":["\"In da Club\" by 50 Cent","\"Crazy Train\" by Ozzy Osbourne","\"Baby Got Back\" by Sir Mix-a-Lot"],"question":"Which song begins with the lyrics: \"I saw a werewolf with a Chinese menu in his hand...\"?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"H. G. Wells","incorrectAnswers":["Neil Gaiman","Arthur C. Clarke","C. S. Lewis"],"question":"Which author wrote 'The Island of Doctor Moreau'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Robert Louis Stevenson","incorrectAnswers":["Oscar Wilde","Agatha Christie","Joseph Conrad"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Kidnapped'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Gary Glitter","incorrectAnswers":["Kajagoogoo","Vicki Lawrence","Spandau Ballet"],"question":"'Rock And Roll (Part 2)' was a hit in 1972 by which artist?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Asia","incorrectAnswers":["Africa","North America","South America"],"question":"Which Of The World's Continents Has The Highest Population? ","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Indo-European","incorrectAnswers":["Turkic","Niger–Congo","Austronesian"],"question":"The language 'Assamese' belongs to which language family?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Blink-182","incorrectAnswers":["Green Day","Nirvana","Foo Fighters"],"question":"Which band is Travis Barker the drummer for?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Juan Valdez","incorrectAnswers":["Emilio Estefan","Pablo Escobar","Fidel Castro"],"question":"Which of these men is a fictional character used to market Colombian coffee growers, and is always seen with his mule named Conchita?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Suriname","incorrectAnswers":["Marshall Islands","Nauru","Uruguay"],"question":"Paramaribo is the capital city of which country?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Saint John's","incorrectAnswers":["Havana","Monaco","Moroni"],"question":"What is the capital city of Antigua and Barbuda?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Sandra Bullock","incorrectAnswers":["Charlize Theron","Emma Thompson","Maggie Smith"],"question":"Which actress has starred in films including Gravity and Crash?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Gorbachev","incorrectAnswers":["Yeltsin","Putin","Khrushchev"],"question":"Who was the last president of the Soviet Union?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Midnight Cowboy","incorrectAnswers":["Ghost","Taxi Driver","The Manchurian Candidate"],"question":"Which film contains the character 'Ratso Rizzo'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Hades","incorrectAnswers":["Zeus","Poseidon","Apollo"],"question":"Which Greek god took Persephone to be his queen in the underworld after she ate his pomegranate seeds?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"\"September\" by Earth, Wind & Fire","incorrectAnswers":["\"Yo Home to Bel-Air\"","\"What I Got\" by Sublime","\"American Pie\" by Don McLean"],"question":"Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Do you remember, the 21st night of September?\"?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Ribbon pasta","incorrectAnswers":["Tubular pasta","Shaped pasta","Strand pasta"],"question":"What type of pasta is fettuccine?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Finland","incorrectAnswers":["Italy","Spain","Portugal"],"question":"Where would you find the city of Helsinki?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Paul Bettany","incorrectAnswers":["Robert Downey Jr.","Mark Ruffalo","Benicio Del Toro"],"question":"The role of Vision in the Marvel Cinematic Universe is played by which actor?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Antoine François Prévost","incorrectAnswers":["Émile Zola","Alphonse Daudet","Alexandre Dumas"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Manon Lescaut'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Wolf","incorrectAnswers":["Tiger","Lion","Bear"],"question":"In the play Macbeth, the witches' cauldron contains the tooth of which animal?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Sequere pecuniam","incorrectAnswers":["In absentia lucis, tenebrae vincunt","Carpe diem","Memento vivere"],"question":"Which of these Latin phrases means 'Follow the money'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Macau","incorrectAnswers":["Taipei","Taiwan","Hong Kong"],"question":"Which Portuguese colony reverted to China in December 1999?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Aqueduct","incorrectAnswers":["Canal","Forum","Arena"],"question":"What did the Romans build to convey water? ","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Scurvy","incorrectAnswers":["Smallpox","Malaria","Yellow fever"],"question":"What disease did the British navy begin issuing daily rations of lemon juice in 1795 to prevent?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Blue","incorrectAnswers":["Yellow","Orange","Green"],"question":"Which of these colors would you find on the flag of Liberia?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Horses","incorrectAnswers":["Whales, dolphins, and porpoise","Skin","Safari animals"],"question":"What is Hippology the study of?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Casino Royale","incorrectAnswers":["The Living Daylights","No Time To Die","Thunderball"],"question":"Which James Bond theme song was performed by Chris Cornell?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"We Have Always Lived in the Castle","incorrectAnswers":["The Stranger","To the Lighthouse","Native Son"],"question":"Which book contains the character 'Mary Katherine Blackwood'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Sofia","incorrectAnswers":["Abuja","Tbilisi","Podgorica"],"question":"What is the capital city of Bulgaria?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Vietnam","incorrectAnswers":["Cambodia","Laos","Thailand"],"question":"In which country is the Mekong River Delta?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Black","incorrectAnswers":["White","Red","Brown"],"question":"What color spots has the common ladybird?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"The Riviera","incorrectAnswers":["The Alps","The Mediterranean","Champagne"],"question":"What is the other name for the Côte d'Azur in France?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Julius Caesar","incorrectAnswers":["Augustus Caesar","Claudius","Nero"],"question":"Which Roman ruler oversaw the demise of the Roman Republic to be replaced with a Roman Empire?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"The Seasiders","incorrectAnswers":["The Canaries","The Robins","The Blades"],"question":"What is the nickname of the English football team Blackpool?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A gang","incorrectAnswers":["A watch","A muster","A bevy"],"question":"What is the word for a group of elk?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Goalkeeper","incorrectAnswers":["Wing back","Centre Half","Linesman"],"question":"In football (soccer), which player uses their hands stop the opposition scoring?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"The Ides of March","incorrectAnswers":["The Kalends of April","The Ides of May","The Kalends of June"],"question":"When was Julius Caesar murdered?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Tasman","incorrectAnswers":["Southern","Antipodal","Indian"],"question":"Which sea is located between Australia and New Zealand?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"A tank","incorrectAnswers":["A helicopter","A submarine","A fighter plane"],"question":"What type of war vehicle is the M26 Pershing and the M4 Sherman?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Crudites","incorrectAnswers":["Amouse Bouche","Béchamel","Poisson"],"question":"In French cooking, what is the word for an appetizer of raw vegetables?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Voltaire","incorrectAnswers":["Socrates","Martin Heidegger","Bertrand Russell"],"question":"Which philosopher famously said 'All is for the best in the best of all possible worlds'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Soccer","incorrectAnswers":["Basketball","Volleyball","Rugby"],"question":"With which sport is Pelé associated?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Settlers of Catan","incorrectAnswers":["Risk","Monopoly","Clue"],"question":"In which classic board game do players build roads, villages and cities to collect resources?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Julia Roberts","incorrectAnswers":["Jodie Foster","Cameron Diaz","Charlize Theron"],"question":"Which actress has featured in films including Ocean's Eleven and Pretty Woman?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Isaac Asimov","incorrectAnswers":["Ursula K. Le Guin","Philip K. Dick","Stephen King"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Second Foundation'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Nepal","incorrectAnswers":["Bangladesh","Thailand","Cambodia"],"question":"Which of these countries borders People's Republic of China?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Bitter Sweet Symphony","incorrectAnswers":["Got to Be Real","Seasons in the Sun","Lovin' You"],"question":"The Verve had a one hit wonder in 1997 with which song?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Wayne Enterprises","incorrectAnswers":["Superhero Inc.","Gotham Corp.","The Dark Knight Co."],"question":"What is the name of the fictional company owned by Batman?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"White Fang","incorrectAnswers":["Cujo","Where the Red Fern Grows","Balto"],"question":"What is the follow-up tale to \"The Call of the Wild\" by Jack London?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Kylie Minogue","incorrectAnswers":["Madonna","Mika","Hikaru Utada"],"question":"Which music artist released the song 'All the Lovers'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"2018","incorrectAnswers":["2016","2017","2019"],"question":"Avengers: Infinity War was released in which year?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Nepal","incorrectAnswers":["Colombia","Korea","Argentina"],"question":"Which country is associated with the drink rakshi?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"For The Win","incorrectAnswers":["Free The Whales","Found This Website","Food To Wine"],"question":"What do people mean when type the letters 'FTW' in a message on the internet?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"We Can Work It Out","incorrectAnswers":["American Woman","Gloria","Woodstock"],"question":"Which song was originally recorded by The Beatles and was later covered by Stevie Wonder?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Armenia","incorrectAnswers":["Saint Kitts and Nevis","Moldova","Mongolia"],"question":"Yerevan is the capital city of which country?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Spain ","incorrectAnswers":["Russia","The United Kingdom","Greece"],"question":"From where does the fortified wine Sherry originate?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Starboard","incorrectAnswers":["Port","Bow","Stern"],"question":"What is the name of the right side of a sailing ship?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Annie Hall","incorrectAnswers":["The Goodbye Girl","Julia","Star Wars"],"question":"Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1977?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Avocado ","incorrectAnswers":["Cucumber","Tomato","Mango"],"question":"Which Is The Main Ingredient Of Guacamole?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"history","correctAnswer":"Austria","incorrectAnswers":["Argentina","Belgium","The United States"],"question":"Which country was Kurt Waldheim, the former Secretary-General of the United Nations, from?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Overexposed","incorrectAnswers":["Oversaturated","Underexposed","Undersaturated"],"question":"What is it called when a photograph is excessively bright due to too much light?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"What Hath God Wrought?","incorrectAnswers":["Testing Testing Testing","Good Morning Victory ","You Smell"],"question":"What was the first ever message sent via morse code?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"Gouache","incorrectAnswers":["Pastiche","Collage","Bertuide"],"question":"What is the word for a method of watercolor painting prepared with a more gluey base, producing a less transparent effect?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Morse code","incorrectAnswers":["Binary code","ASCII code","Unicode"],"question":"What is the name of the communication method represented by a series of dots and dashes?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"general_knowledge","correctAnswer":"Calico","incorrectAnswers":["Corduroy","Chiffon","Cashmere"],"question":"What is the name of the cotton fabric, named for a city in India, made from unbleached, and often not fully processed cotton?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"The Netherlands","incorrectAnswers":["Belgium","Denmark","Austria"],"question":"From What Country Does Advocaat Originate?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Mexico","incorrectAnswers":["Israel","Indonesia","Greece"],"question":"In which country would you find Chichen Itza?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"A glider","incorrectAnswers":["A leaper","A flyer","A hanger"],"question":"What name is often used to refer to a type of flying possum?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Mexico","incorrectAnswers":["Cuba","Chile","Paraguay"],"question":"In which country is the city of Guadalajara?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"Black","incorrectAnswers":["Nine","Green","Yellow"],"question":"In German, what is the meaning of the word 'schwarz'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Olivia Newton-John","incorrectAnswers":["Tippi Hedren","Audrey Hepburn","Kathy Bates"],"question":"Which actress played the role of Sandy Olsson in Grease?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"ants","incorrectAnswers":["fresh water environments, particularly lakes","the Soviet Union","prehistoric metazoans "],"question":"What is Myrmecology the study of?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"sport_and_leisure","correctAnswer":"Greece","incorrectAnswers":["Argentina","Japan","Australia"],"question":"Which Country Hosted The 2004 Summer Olympics?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"An Infant","incorrectAnswers":["A Pup","A Bunny","A Piglet"],"question":"What is a baby monkey known as?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"\"Truth Hurts\" by Lizzo","incorrectAnswers":["\"I'm Real (Murder Remix) by Jennifer Lopez and Ja Rule","\"Old Man\" by Neil Young","\"Chimpan-A to Chimpan-Z\" by Troy McClure"],"question":"Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Why men great 'till they gotta be great?\"?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"The Simpsons","incorrectAnswers":["South Park","Family Guy","SpongeBob SquarePants"],"question":"Which iconic  animated sitcom includes a teenage boy named Bart?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Mark Hamill","incorrectAnswers":["Harrison Ford","John Daniels","James Earl Jones"],"question":"Who played the role of Luke Skywalker in Star Wars?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Shortness of breath","incorrectAnswers":["Fever","Weight loss","Headache"],"question":"Which of the following is a symptom of asthma?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"United States of America","incorrectAnswers":["El Salvador","Honduras","Nicaragua"],"question":"Which of these countries borders Mexico?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"India","incorrectAnswers":["United Kingdom","Indonesia","Ireland"],"question":"Which region of the world uses '.in' at the end of its web addresses?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"geography","correctAnswer":"Rhode Island ","incorrectAnswers":["Hawaii","Maine","Vermont"],"question":"Which Is The Smallest State In The USA? ","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"food_and_drink","correctAnswer":"Bushmills ","incorrectAnswers":["Teeling","Tullamore","Jamesons"],"question":"What is the oldest distillery in the world?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Double Indemnity","incorrectAnswers":["Casino","Dune","The Great Escape"],"question":"Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'An insurance representative lets a housewife seduce him into a scheme of insurance fraud and murder.'","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"The Doors","incorrectAnswers":["Styx","The Pussycat Dolls","Three 6 Mafia"],"question":"Which American rock band released the album 'Morrison Hotel'?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"music","correctAnswer":"Mizmar","incorrectAnswers":["Harpsichord","Banjo","Lyre"],"question":"Which of these is a woodwind instrument?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"film_and_tv","correctAnswer":"Brie Larson","incorrectAnswers":["Zoe Saldana","Karen Gillan","Hayley Atwell"],"question":"The role of Captain Marvel in the Marvel Cinematic Universe is played by which actor?","difficulty":"medium"},{"category":"arts_and_literature","correctAnswer":"The Chronicles of Narnia","incorrectAnswers":["Voyages Extraordinaires","Harry Potter","Percy Jackson & the Olympians"],"question":"In which book series does 'Prince Caspian' appear?","difficulty":"easy"},{"category":"society_and_culture","correctAnswer":"T35","incorrectAnswers":["DB5","Polo","Model 3"],"question":"Which of these was a model of car made by Bugatti?","difficulty":"hard"},{"category":"science","correctAnswer":"Ritalin","incorrectAnswers":["Amoxicillin","Prozac","Zoloft"],"question":"Which of these medicines is often used to treat attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?","difficulty":"medium"},